(Leonard:)Wait, are we really going to Long Beach?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
SHELDON:
Leonard? Leonard? Leonard?
(Leonard:)Let it go, Sheldon.
(Leonard:)The murderer was the first mate
whether it makes sense to you or not.
(Sheldon:)No, that's the least of our worries.
I've been doing research on addiction...
(Sheldon:)...both the biochemical
and behavioral aspects...
(Sheldon:)...and I think there's a problem
with the current version of our lie.
What are you talking about?
It's fine, she bought it, it's over.
(Sheldon:)Sadly, it's not.
(Sheldon:)Substance abuse is a lifelong struggle.
(Sheldon:)But beyond that,
I have realized the Leo I described...
(Sheldon:)- ...would not have agreed to go to rehab.
- Why not?
Because Leo's a middle child.
There's no Leo. How can you say that?
(Sheldon:)You didn't read the bio, did you?